milkadeal.com 2014-08-24

# Privacy Policy - MilkADeal

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the MilkADeal website (collectively, the "website" is located at www.MilkADeal.com).

Your privacy is critically important to us. At MilkADeal we have a few fundamental principles:

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, LEAVE THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS THE WEBSITE.

* **Types of Information Collected and Uses of Collected Information**

We collect two types of information about our Website Users. They are Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

Personally Identifiable Information. We define Personally Identifiable Information as information that identifies a specific End User. When you perform certain activities on the Website, such as creating an account, purchasing a product or service from us or our partners, submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums, requesting information about our services, taking part in a survey, entering a contest or sweepstakes sponsored by us or our partners, submitting a review, sending us or our partners feedback, submitting an affiliate agreement, applying for a job vacancy, posting a video or signing up for special offers from third parties through the Website (collectively, "Identification Activities"), we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. It is optional for you to engage in an Identification Activity. Should you decide to engage in an Identification Activity, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information about yourself, such as your first and last name, mailing address, email address, telephone number and date of birth. When you order products or services, we may also ask you to furnish us with your credit card number, expiration date and authentication codes or transaction related information. Subject to the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some is identified as voluntary. If the mandatory information for a particular activity is not provided upon request, you will not be permitted to engage in that activity.

Refer Friends. If you decide to use our referral service or buy a deal for a friend, we will request for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email with the gift you bought for them or inviting him or her to visit the site.

To request that we remove this information from our database, your friend may contact us at support@MilkADeal.com.

We use Personally Identifiable Information to provide products and services to you, enhance the operation of the Website, administer sweepstakes and contests, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze Website use, improve our product and service offerings, and to tailor your experience with third parties. Aside from that, if you use our Website to send information or a product to another person, we may store your personal information. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot, accomplish administrative tasks, get in touch with you, enforce our agreements with you, including our Website Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable Malaysian law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information. We define Non-Personally Identifiable Information as information that does not identify a specific End User. Like many other Websites, the Website automatically collects certain non-identifiable information regarding Website users, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer, the IP address of your Internet Service Provider, the date and time you access the Web Site, the Internet address of the Website from which you linked directly to the Website, the operating system you are using, the sections of the Web Site you visit, the Website pages accessed and information viewed, and the materials you post to or download from the Website. This non- identifiable information is used for our Website and system administration purposes as well as to improve the Website. We, and/or our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers, may automatically collect this information when you visit our Website through the use of electronic tools such as Cookies.

We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to administer the Website, troubleshoot, analyze trends, gather general demographic data, and comply with relevant Malaysian law. We may share this information with our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers to measure the overall effectiveness of our content, online advertising campaigns and programming.

* **Release of Personally Identifiable Information**

We will not share, sell, rent, or trade your Personally Identifiable Information for marketing purposes with other parties except as provided below:

In general, Personally Identifiable Information you submit to us is used by us to provide you access to MilkADeal, to improve MilkADeal, to better tailor the features, performance, and support of MilkADeal and to offer you additional information, opportunities, promotions and functionality from us, our partners or our advertisers at your request. Additionally, we do share your content preferences and other information with the social network with which you have connected to MilkADeal, along with those companies and persons you have asked us to share your information with.

We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third-party service providers who work on behalf of or with us to provide some of the services and features of MilkADeal and to help us communicate with you. Examples of such services include sending email, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments (including credit card payments), and providing customer service.

We may share some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information (other than credit card information) with Merchants whose Deals you have purchased in order to aid redemption. If you do not want us to use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information collected about you in the manner identified in this Privacy Policy, you may not use MilkADeal. 

We may remarket your information. Remarketing is a way for us to connect with users, based upon your previous interactions with the MilkADeal Website. Third-party marketing vendors may be hired by MilkADeal to perform remarketing services.

In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personally Identifiable Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of ours or that acquirer’s assets may continue to process your Personally Identifiable Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We may share your information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary for our Protection and the Protection of Others. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website. You hereby consent to us sharing your Personally Identifiable Information under the circumstances described herein.

* **Release of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
We may disclose and/or share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with our Partners, Affiliates and Advertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information with "Third Party Advertisers" or "Third Party Advertising Companies".

* **Updating and Correcting Information**  
You may modify any of your Personally Identifiable Information by logging into your account and accessing the "my account" section of the Website, sending us an email at support@MilkADeal.com or writing to us at 21 Jalan Datuk Sulaiman 4, Taman Tun Dr. Ismail, Kuala Lumpur 60000. Please include your name, address and email address, and what information you would like to update when contacting us.

If you choose to store credit card information on the site, you may delete your credit card information at any time by going to the "my account" section of your profile

.
* **User Choices on Collection and/or Use of Information**  
As discussed above, you can always opt not to provide information, although it may be required to engage in a certain activity on the Website.

As a condition of purchase of our products and services, we will send you Administrative and Promotional emails. We will send you information regarding your account activity and purchases as well as updates about our products and promotional offers. You cannot opt-out of Administrative Emails. “Administrative Emails” relate to a User’s activity on the Website, and include emails regarding a particular User’s account, requests or inquiries, and purchases of products and services. In contrast to Administrative Emails, however, you do have a choice with respect to Promotional Emails. Promotional Emails advertise our products and services, including exclusive sales and other offers, and/or the products and services of our Advertisers and Affiliates. If you do not want to receive Promotional Emails from us, you may elect to opt-out of receiving Promotional Emails at any time after registering by e-mailing us at support@MilkADeal.com, by writing to us at the address contained herein, or by hitting the “unsubscribe” button at the bottom of any of our e- mails. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Promotional Emails you do not want to receive.

* **Data Tracking**  
Cookies. A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. MilkADeal uses cookies to help MilkADeal identify and track visitors, their usage of MilkADeal website, and their website access preferences. MilkADeal visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using MilkADeal’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of MilkADeal’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

* **Security of Information**  
We work to keep our servers, applications and databases secure and free from unauthorized access and use, by using physical, administrative and technological measures to protection the information we maintain. Unfortunately, no one can guarantee 100% security. If you have particular security concerns about certain personal information, please do not transmit that information over the Internet.

* **Privacy Policies of Third Party Websites**  
This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on www.MilkADeal.com. Other websites that may be accessible through this Website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Therefore, if you link to any such website, we urge you review the website’s privacy policy as we cannot be responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

* **Miscellaneous Privacy Issues**  
Children. Children under the age of 18 may not use the Website. MilkADeal does not knowingly collect personal information from minor children. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide personal information on this Website without their permission.

Facebook Connect. The MilkADeal Site allows users to access Facebook Connect to interact with friends and to share on Facebook. If you are logged into MilkADeal and Facebook, when you click on "Connect with Facebook" your profiles will merge if the email addresses match. If the email addresses don't match, we ask you if you want to merge them and you must enter your MilkADeal password to validate that they control that account. If you are already logged into MilkADeal but not logged into Facebook, when you click on "Connect with Facebook" you will be prompted to enter your Facebook credentials or to "Sign up for Facebook." By proceeding you are allowing the MilkADeal Site to access your information and you are agreeing to the Facebook Terms of Use in your use of MilkADeal Sites.

* **Privacy Policy Changes**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, MilkADeal may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in MilkADeal’s sole discretion. MilkADeal encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of notice on our home page. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

* **Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, please contact us.

MilkADeal Sdn. Bhd. (928546-V)  
22-3 Jalan PJU 8/5G  
Damansara Perdana  
47820 Petaling Jaya  
Selangor, Malaysia.

Tel: +603-7725 2180 / +603-5021 8398  
Fax: +603-7725 2160

Customer Service Inquiries | support@MilkADeal.com

_

This privacy statement was last modified on 17 January 2011.

_
